The island is flying?!
Can this... truly be happening?!
Just how powerful is Kaido?!
What?!
Why?!
How come?!
Marco the Phoenix?!
Well then, let's try this!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Chopper!
Hot! Hot! I'm burning!
Hey! That's going too far!
I thought we were on the same side!
Marco!
Marco...!
They sure are testy...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Chopper! I'll put it out!
It's burning my arm!
It'll scorch me too–
Or not?
This flame...
Ouch! Ouch! Ow, ow...
Chopper, you can relax!
Huh?
It's really hot–
Or not?
I'm on fire but I'm not getting burned!
This flame is comfortably...
warm...
– Dr. Chopper!
We're ready to produce the antibodies!
Come quickly!
It's a swarm of ice ogres!
Miyagi! Tristan! Get out of here!
Gotta warm them up one way or another!
Phoenix Pyreapple!
Yeow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Oh, it's not that hot...
The chill in my body is fading!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
What?!
Wh-What was I...?!
Omasa!
Thank goodness! You came to your senses!
Omasa...!
Well, it's like you were saying.
It's sapping your body heat.
Once your stamina runs out,
you'll turn back into an ogre!
I only bought you a bit of time!
You're a lifesaver!
Time's just what the doctor ordered!
Miyagi! Tristan!
Are you two okay?!
Y-Yes!
We're fine!
Let's hurry and get to work!
We'll give you the support you need!
Thank you! I can focus if I'm in that tower!
Marco!
He and that damn tanuki really
know how to chap my ass!
Hey, you bums! Catch that tanuki already!
Why would he bother
saving your lousy asses?!
But... that tanuki...
Keep your eyes on the prize!
If you don't wanna bite the dust,
crush that tanuki and take back the antibody!
I see... I think I've got the gist of the situation.
Hey, Roronoa!
Weren't you on your way
to slice 'n dice Kaido?
If you wanna get to the rooftop...
I'll give you a lift!
You guys are too good to be
dealing with these chumps!
But Chopper needs our support...!
Don't worry... Sir Skeleton!
We'll hold the line for Sir Tanuki!
Thanks, you guys! I'm counting on you!
Hold it, you son of a bitch!
Apoo!
Give me back the antibody...!
If I lose it...
my ass is freakin' grass!
Give it a rest!
He won't stay down!
I don't mind taking on one more job!
Sir Tanuki, hurry into the tower!
– Apoo!
This guy...
Drake?!
So he really has switched sides!
Roronoa Zoro. If you would
consider me an ally...
then I'll hold them here while you go ahead!
At least you know how
to bet on the winning horse!
Sanji! Sanji!
Perhaps Sanji sensed a powerful foe
and went to hold them back on the third floor!
Maybe...!
Guess my observation haki isn't that good yet.
I'm not picking up Sanji's presence at all!
Do you feel something, Jinbe?!
Yeah...
There are quite a few enemies in here...
And...
they're quite strong!
Seems like one of us
should remain on this floor!
I'll create an opening. You go on ahead!
Let's do this!
General...
Launcher!
Time to raise a little hell!
General...
Cannon!
Get back, men!
Who the hell fires something so haphazardly?!
You're asking for it!
I dig the look, bro!
A triceratops!
So you're a dinosaur!
Just give up! This is the strongest
creature that ever lived!
You'll be nothing but scrap
when I'm done with you!
There's no scratching the sheen of Wapometal!
It's the Soaring Six!
Where did they go?!
I am ever so vexed!
I shall crack her detestable head
wide open! That bitch!
He ran off that way!
Slow down, silly!
Wait for us!
Damn! What is this?!
Let me out!
You can stop struggling now...
Be a good boy... Don't try to run.
After all...
didn't you say that you loved me?
Stay by my side forever. I'll make you my pet.
Don't be ridiculous! I...
I have somewhere to be!
But...
everywhere...
I look...
it's women, women, women...!
Is this...
heaven?
He's clearly lost it.
You're absolutely precious...
So Straw Hat went on ahead...
This'll be a real headache for ol' Kaido...
Would you kindly stop...
picking on my men?
Former Warlord Jinbe, Knight of the Sea,
acting with all the decorum of a child?
I am the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Would you do me the honor
of using this worthier title?
Oh, my bad.
I caught a glimpse of you back in your Warlord days...
What?!
Well, it's no big deal.
Who are you?
Man, who could I possibly be?
Perhaps removing your mask
will jog my memory.
I'd love to see you try.
We can hide here for a bit
since this room has long gone unnoticed.
What am I seeing?
A statue of a dragon.
It once stood at the entry point of the island,
but it was placed in here after my friend broke it.
Your friend?
Yes...
A few years ago...
he came to kill my father!
What gives? This place is deserted...
Intruders!
If you're not Kaido, get lost!
Ace!
Guys, go save the children while you can!
Got it!
Leave it to us!
This one won't stay down!
Who are you?! Tell me your name!
Right back at you!
I'm Ace!
I'm here to take Kaido's head!
I found them! Over here!
Don't be scared. We're getting
all of you out of here.
Yeah, but we need to hurry.
You're pretty tough.
Ace!
All the children are okay!
But we can't find Kaido anywhere!
What?!
My father went on an expedition!
At this very moment...
not a single officer is here!
Your father?!
– What?!
So she's Kaido's daughter?!
I'm Yamato!
I think it's about time you
stopped tearing up the place!
If you have time to wonder who I am,
then you have time to leave
and return these children to their families!
I'll take you up on that.
But is it wise to let us go?
It's not like I'm under any obligation
to protect this island.
Alright, let's get back to Wano.
Your families are waiting for you.
Truly, we can't thank you enough!
You sure, Ace?
That means going back
to the mainland without you.
That's right. Keep them safe. I'll catch up later.
I'm not convinced someone as strong
as you isn't at least one of their captains...
Let's settle this!
I was bored anyway.
Let's fight!
Fire Fist!
What's the story? Shouldn't someone
as strong as you be out at sea?!
It's all his fault...
Kaido's fault!
Of all the people to have as a father...
It's all your father's fault?
That's your excuse?
You can't...
choose your parents, Yamato!
Shut up! Don't you think I know that?!
Do you really?
Physical shackles are one thing,
but if you hate your father this much...
why shackle your heart as well?!
Yamato!
What do you want to do?!
I admit...
I was holding myself back.
But now I realize...
I wanna set out to sea and go on adventures!
I wanna live freely like Oden!
Set out to sea...
To sea...
I wanna leave this damn island...!
I wanna live freely!
That's the spirit, Yamato!
It's good to want those things!
Now you know what to do.
Yeah!
And he came home in tatters!
When we were kids, he got us
into all kinds of trouble!
Your little brother sure is something!
Right?!
So tell me, what's it like out there?!
Are there a lot of young up-and-comers?!
Young...? Let me think...
Everyone's talking about Caven-something.
Yeah?!
Well, I'm in a class of my own,
but I heard some dangerous guys
are running wild in every sea.
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
There's Kid in the south...
Law in the north and Bege in the west.
But the toughest one of all
will set sail in a few years...
My kid brother!
He'll blow 'em all outta the water!
You sure do like to talk about your brother.
So what?! You should listen!
Ow, ow, ow!
You... That hurts!
H-Hey, stop!
The truth is I'm the one
who broke this dragon statue first.
But he said...
"Let this be a warning
to Kaido that I'll be back!"
I see...
I was unaware that a pirate
once tried to save Wano...
It pissed off my father,
but in the end, he never met Ace.
Wait...
Your father?
Didn't I mention Kaido being my father?
Wha– Hey, don't be so scared!
Hey, but I really do hate him!
Like I said, I'm Oden!
That is even more confusing!
I'm not scary! I hate Kaido!
I longed for the sea and adventure,
so I became Oden, who lived freely!
We understand for the most part.
Thank you for tending to us!
Stop being so formal and get over here!
But Yamato,
where is this would-be savior of Wano now?
Ace...
died two years ago.
Otama, you knew Ace?!
Yes, he was like a brother to me!
I decided to believe in Ace
and try to become a kunoichi,
but Big Bro Luffy was mean and said to me...
Ace is dead.
He said it to me out of the blue.
It made me so sad.
Oh, sorry about that.
That's just the way he is.
But y'know, Otama,
it was really hard for Luffy, too.
Back when it happened...
Huh?
He's ruining it!
Listen up, folks!
Put a stop to Marco!
Don't let him run free!
C'mon, he saved us...
But if we don't do what His Awesomeness
wants, he'll kill us anyway...
Don't just stand there!
I gave you an order!
I won't be facing Kaido directly at this point.
Nico Robin! Skeleton Man!
You've got places to be!
Get to the castle!
Now's our chance.
If you insist!
Go to hell, Marco!
You're finished, Marco the Phoenix!
You ready?
Do it!
Damn that Marco!
Nice going!
You're pretty relaxed for someone
about to face down an Emperor!
Why should I be scared of Kaido?
If my captain gives the order, I follow it.
Look at me, rooting for Straw Hat– No...
rooting for all you Worst Generation punks!
I wonder how he would've felt hearing his
brother picked a fight with an Emperor, too...
I'm begging you, Pops!
I said no, you little shit!
Ace, I've told you plenty of times now...
who the 2nd Division
commander was before you...
and why the position was vacant for so long.
Wano practices a policy of isolation,
so information never comes out.
We were unaware that Lord Oden
had died until several years after the fact.
We toyed with the idea of
raiding Wano, but to what end?
Can you imagine the toll it would take?
The toll?
Then, let me go by myself!
I made a promise...
Kozuki Oden couldn't take that guy down...
Meaning you couldn't beat him
on your best day!
Don't overestimate yourself, Ace!
Y'know, Oden's strength was the real deal!
You really wanna take down
the big shots, Commander Ace!
Give it a rest, Teach!
Ace isn't motivated by hunting "big shots."
Dammit...
I need to get stronger
so I can fulfill my promise...
That's what you're shouldering, huh?
Ace, if Pops ever gives the go-ahead,
do not forget to extend an invitation my way.
Count me in, too.
In that case, we can probably
kick his ass now...
How are you still
overestimating the situation...?
Marco!
Don't think we'd just let you through!
Besides, all the samurai up top are dead by now!
And when Kozuki Oden's son
is dead, the battle will be over!
Wano shall be reborn as
the pirate empire of New Onigashima!
If that's what you believe,
then you really have a screw loose!
Stop squawking, little bird!
Damn! Is he invincible?!
What kind of power is that?
You're up against the force of a new era now!
The Beast Pirates will crush this "new era,"
along with everything else!
Wha–
Now, now... Just let him pass!
And up you go!
You seriously just threw me?!
What?!
B...
Big Bro Luffy is Ace's little bro?!
That's right.
You didn't know?
Because when I mentioned Ace,
he said so casually...
Ace is dead.
I said some mean things to Big Bro...
He would've been mean right back
if it had bothered him.
Don't worry!
But...
Big Bro... I'm sorry!
Like I said, don't worry.
Anyway, let's give this
"Otama Strategy" of yours a shot!
What?!
This person you speak of was Roger's son,
and Luffy's older brother?!
Is that true?!
Mm-hm.
You all brought Luffy to Wano, right?
That is correct...
There are as many pirates as there are stars
in the sky, but they're the ones you met...
and you brought them to this country...
I can't imagine this as anything but fate!
Because...
Luffy's name bears the initial D!
Yummy!
Fire really hits the spot!
Delicious!
I'm so stuffed now!
I'm fully recharged!
Did you finish your meals?
Yes, Mama!
I'm good to go!
Okay then, let's go!
Straw Hat isn't here yet?
Hey, Kaido!
You can kill as many as you want
as long as you leave Nico Robin alive.
Don't you have a member of the three-eye
people who can read the ancient script?
Oh, Pudding?
I'm not sure she can.
I can't wait for her true awakening anymore.
Yeah, that make sense...
This is about all we can do to assist,
so please, go on ahead!
These are the stairs to the rooftop!
Thanks, Shishimamushi!
It's Shishilian.
Yeah, I'll never forget it...
The way you guys defended
Raizo with your lives!
Thank you!
Later!
So where are you planning on
dropping this island?
There is a castle in the Flower Capital
that symbolizes the Kozuki.
I heard they're having a festival.
Quite a lot of people will die.
Who cares?
It's easy to get more slaves...
It'll be a glorious capital.
And the lode poneglyph?
Is it there?
Your true colors are already showing!
Don't give me that!
You're like a little brother to me!
On that day when Rocks
was defeated at God Valley,
I gave you the Mythical Fish-Fish Fruit.
You're indebted to me for life, Kaido!
Whatever!
Let's go get it, then we'll talk!
Let's get the One Piece!